<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Loser on Evi1haxor</title>
    <link>/loser/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Loser on Evi1haxor</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 12:14:34 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/loser/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Thinkathon &#39;20</title>
      <link>/loser/thinkathon2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 21:12:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/loser/thinkathon2/</guid>
      <description>Mosquiteer&amp;rsquo;s Gambit Having my room just beside the garden, I evoked my hatred toward these little sanguivorous flies. Just when India is struggling with a global pandemic, the yearly malaria crisis may come on the doorstep any time now. Although the government does what it has to, but I ask, is it the best we can do? Every year, literally waiting for it to hit us? One way, also proposed in the literature, is to kill all the mosquitoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Colonising Mars</title>
      <link>/loser/occmars/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 13:48:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/loser/occmars/</guid>
      <description>Environmental Biotechnology Strategies for Planetary Colonisation Past ten years have witnessed some of the best innovations in space technology. It has everything that industry requires to reap- novel technology, business model, service design. With its disruptive reusable two-side booster technology, SpaceX is on its peak, only to get better with time. Decreasing costs of the launch over the years ratifies the smart engineering techniques that are being executed in the development of new space vehicles and launchers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zmsai</title>
      <link>/loser/zettelkastenai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 19:44:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/loser/zettelkastenai/</guid>
      <description>Productivity is the core value of work. In the modern economy, where at every step one has to face cut-throat competition, it is becoming increasingly important to produce at an elite level. Professional activities demand an affiliation to the task at hand that can push one’s cognitive capability to its limits. In order to thrive in this new economy, one needs to master two core abilities- first, the ability to quickly master hard things and second, the ability to produce at the highest level in terms of both quality and speed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cancer Subtyping Algorithm</title>
      <link>/loser/btp_report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 10:36:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/loser/btp_report/</guid>
      <description>Cancer Subtype Discovery from Multi-modal Omic Data Needless to state how bad a disease cancer is. As per WHO, cancer is the second-largest non-infectious reason for the death by natural cause in humans. The earliest cancer research dates back to the 1700s. So it has been around for a very long time, but there is no promising cure for this disease yet. We have found the cure of so many diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CoVup Setu</title>
      <link>/loser/covup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 12:30:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/loser/covup/</guid>
      <description>Because services that have setu in their names are rad&amp;rsquo; cool.
Github/CoVup repository 1 2 3 4 5 6 7  ├── meta.json ├── README.md ├── scripts │ ├── main.py └── templates ├── announce.txt └── subscribers.txt   I have made such arrangements (using WayScript) that the script scripts/main.py would trigger itself off every day and send an email to all the subscribers regarding the latest CoV pandemic stats about their district (like active cases, confirmed cases, recovered cases and deceased cases).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>