<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Archit&#39;s Website on Evi1haxor</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Archit&#39;s Website on Evi1haxor</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to AI</title>
      <link>/elixir/ai-intro-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 19:08:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/elixir/ai-intro-1/</guid>
      <description>Movies have been portraying AI in some of the other forms for decades. Regardless of how stunning and fascinating they may look, in order to make their movies entertaining, the makers of such movies reflect various narratives about AI that is shaping our perception of the future of human civilisation. Some represent them as evil, so much so that it is believed that considering the pace of advancement in AI and machine learning technology, one day a true AI would be made that would exceed human intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Python</title>
      <link>/elixir/pyc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/elixir/pyc/</guid>
      <description>Many times programmers new to python find the idea of python bieng an interpreted language very unconvincing. It&amp;rsquo;s that mysterious .pyc files and __pycache__ directory that gets generated as they run their script that seed their confusion.
Python is a high-level language. Simply put, unlike compiled language, in case of python, the source code does not get converted into an object code (followed by linking in case of compiled languages). Python code directly spits out the results hence bypassing the conversion to the object code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boyd&#39;s Law of Iteration</title>
      <link>/elixir/byds-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 14:12:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/elixir/byds-law/</guid>
      <description>The following content is taken from my twitter thread about Boyd&amp;rsquo;s Law of Iteration.
Boyd&amp;rsquo;s law of iteration: Speed of iteration beats the quality of iteration It was some time around the 1950s when Colonel John Boyd, an accomplished fighter pilot and strategist, got himself obsessed with an &amp;lsquo;anomaly&amp;rsquo; pertaining to the comparative performance of two fighter jets of that era- F-86s and Mig-15s.
Having indulged in dogfights on both of those jets, he knew both of them very well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Portfolio Website</title>
      <link>/techtrek/hugo-portfolio-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/techtrek/hugo-portfolio-website/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aadhar</title>
      <link>/elixir/aadhar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 00:46:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/elixir/aadhar/</guid>
      <description>Aadhar though revolutionary, but not a new concept. Many countries have been using a similar system even before Aadhar could undergo strong establishment in India. Malaysian MyKad is one good old example, some more are, Indonesian eKTP, Ghana has its NIA, and Abrid is of Brazil. Be that as it may, but Aadhar definitely has given a tug to the Indian kite in its technological involvement. As of May 2018, 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog init</title>
      <link>/elixir/first-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/elixir/first-blog/</guid>
      <description>1 2  blog init echo &amp;#34;Hello World!&amp;#34;   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>