<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Archit&#39;s Website on Evi1haxor</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Archit&#39;s Website on Evi1haxor</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>On Colonising Mars</title>
      <link>/techtrek/occmars/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 13:48:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/techtrek/occmars/</guid>
      <description>Environmental Biotechnology Strategies for Planetary Colonisation Past ten years have witnessed some of the best innovations in space technology. It has everything that industry requires to reap- novel technology, business model, service design. With its disruptive reusable two-side booster technology, SpaceX is on its peak, only to get better with time. Decreasing costs of the launch over the years ratifies the smart engineering techniques that are being executed in the development of new space vehicles and launchers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zmsai</title>
      <link>/techtrek/zettelkastenai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 19:44:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/techtrek/zettelkastenai/</guid>
      <description>Productivity is the core value of work. In the modern economy, where at every step one has to face cut-throat competition, it is becoming increasingly important to produce at an elite level. Professional activities demand an affiliation to the task at hand that can push one’s cognitive capability to its limits. In order to thrive in this new economy, one needs to master two core abilities- first, the ability to quickly master hard things and second, the ability to produce at the highest level in terms of both quality and speed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cancer Subtyping Algorithm</title>
      <link>/techtrek/btp_report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 10:36:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/techtrek/btp_report/</guid>
      <description>Cancer Subtype Discovery from Multi-modal Omic Data Needless to state how bad a disease cancer is. As per WHO, cancer is the second-largest non-infectious reason for the death by natural cause in humans. The earliest cancer research dates back to the 1700s. So it has been around for a very long time, but there is no promising cure for this disease yet. We have found the cure of so many diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to AI</title>
      <link>/elixir/ai-intro-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 19:08:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/elixir/ai-intro-1/</guid>
      <description>Movies have been portraying AI in some or the other forms for decades. Regardless of how stunning and fascinating they may look, in order to make their movies entertaining, their makers reflect various narratives about AI that are shaping our perception of the future of human civilisation. Some represent them as evil, so much so that it is believed that considering the pace of advancement in AI and machine learning technology, one day a true AI would be made that would exceed human intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Python</title>
      <link>/elixir/pyc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/elixir/pyc/</guid>
      <description>Many times programmers new to python find the idea of python bieng an interpreted language very unconvincing. It&amp;rsquo;s that mysterious .pyc files and __pycache__ directory that gets generated as they run their script that seed their confusion.
Python is a high-level language. Simply put, unlike compiled language, in case of python, the source code does not get converted into an object code (followed by linking in case of compiled languages). Python code directly spits out the results hence bypassing the conversion to the object code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boyd&#39;s Law of Iteration</title>
      <link>/elixir/byds-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 14:12:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/elixir/byds-law/</guid>
      <description>The following content is taken from my twitter thread about Boyd&amp;rsquo;s Law of Iteration.
Boyd&amp;rsquo;s law of iteration: Speed of iteration beats the quality of iteration It was some time around the 1950s when Colonel John Boyd, an accomplished fighter pilot and strategist, got himself obsessed with an &amp;lsquo;anomaly&amp;rsquo; pertaining to the comparative performance of two fighter jets of that era- F-86s and Mig-15s.
Having indulged in dogfights on both of those jets, he knew both of them very well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CoVup Setu</title>
      <link>/techtrek/covup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 12:30:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/techtrek/covup/</guid>
      <description>Because services that have setu in their names are rad&amp;rsquo; cool.
Github/CoVup repository 1 2 3 4 5 6 7  ├── meta.json ├── README.md ├── scripts │ ├── main.py └── templates ├── announce.txt └── subscribers.txt   I have made such arrangements (using WayScript) that the script scripts/main.py would trigger itself off every day and send an email to all the subscribers regarding the latest CoV pandemic stats about their district (like active cases, confirmed cases, recovered cases and deceased cases).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aadhar</title>
      <link>/elixir/aadhar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 00:46:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/elixir/aadhar/</guid>
      <description>Aadhar though revolutionary, but not a new concept. Many countries have been using a similar system even before Aadhar could undergo strong establishment in India. Malaysian MyKad is one good old example, some more are, Indonesian eKTP, Ghana has its NIA, and Abrid is of Brazil. Be that as it may, but Aadhar definitely has given a tug to the Indian kite in its technological involvement. As of May 2018, 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog init</title>
      <link>/elixir/first-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/elixir/first-blog/</guid>
      <description>1 2  blog init echo &amp;#34;Hello World!&amp;#34;   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>